skyroam.com 2016-06-23

# "Skyroam | Skyroam Hotspot global mobile hotspot keeps you connected on the road - for only $10 a day."

Sky Travel Services Co., Limited. is committed to respecting and preserving your privacy. This privacy policy and agreement ("Privacy Policy") covers how we collect, use, and treat personal information that you may provide through our website located at skyroam.com (the "Website" or the "Site"). The terms "you" and "your" refer to any visitor at our Website ("Site Visitors"), as well as to any visitors who engage in transactions over the Website (if we include such features on the Site) (each a "Site Customer"). The terms "SKY", "we" and "us" refer to Sky Travel Services Co., Limited. 

1\. Your Consent   
Please read this Privacy Policy carefully; once you consent to this Policy's terms, it creates legal obligations on you and on SKY. We ask you to consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy in different ways, depending on your relationship to the Site. The procedures for consenting to this Policy are (a) less formal if you are a casual Site Visitor, (b) more formal if you are a Site Customer. 

1.1 Consent by Site Visitors   
By accessing and using our Website as a Site Visitor, you are acknowledging that you have read and understood this Privacy Policy and agree to be legally bound by it. If you do not agree with the terms of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our Site. 

1.2 Consent by Site Customers   
If we decide to include features on the Site that allow online transactions, Site Customers submit contact information, and other information, to us via the Website. When you register as a Site Customer via the Site, you will be prompted to click an "I Accept" button linked to this Policy. Clicking "I accept" confirms your agreement to be bound by this Privacy Policy. 

2\. Scope of Policy   
This Privacy Policy applies (i) to anonymous information you provide to us while using our Site, and (ii) to personally identifiable information that you choose to provide to us via the Website, or that provide to us as part of the process of registering online as a Site Customer. This Policy does not apply to other information we may collect through traditional, offline means. 

3\. The Information We Collect, and Our Uses of this Information   
We will not share personally identifiable information you provide via the Website with any third party, other than as expressly disclosed in this policy. By "personally identifiable information" we mean information that identifies you, such as your name, mailing address, or email address. We collect information from you at different points on our Website, and use this information as follows: 

3.1 Registration Information   
As a Site Visitor or a Site Customer, you may provide personally identifiable information to us, in connection with requests for information, or for other reasons. 

3.2 Emergency Information   
As a Site Customer, you may provide personal information, emergency contact information, and medical information to us, in connection with requests for information or for other reasons. This information is requested to help you, and designated emergency personnel, in the event of an emergency, and to configure and personalize your SKY device and/or experience. 

3.3 Processing Requests and Transactions   
When you make a request of us via our Website, we will use any personally identifiable information that you provide in connection with that request for the purposes of processing and responding to that request. In each instance where you make a request under our Website, we use the information you provide to us solely for the purpose of fulfilling your request. 

3.4 Newsletters, Informational Notices and Bulletins   
Periodically, we may choose to send newsletters, bulletins, marketing materials, or other information to you, and will use personally identifiable information to send such communications. If we choose to undertake such communications, you will have the ability to opt out of receiving these communications as provided in Section 5. 

3.5 Anonymous, Aggregate Information.   
"Aggregate Information" is information that does not identify you, and may include statistical information that may range from statistical information and analyses concerning the number of transactions through our Site or services, and the pages on our Site that users visit most frequently. We use Aggregate Information to analyze the effectiveness of our Site, to improve our services and our Website, and for other similar purposes. In addition, from time to time, we may undertake or commission statistical and other summary analyses of (i) the general behavior and characteristics of our Site Visitors, (ii) the effect of our programs on, and the behavior of our Site Visitors, and (iii) the general characteristics of visitors at our Site and participants in our services. We may share these analyses and Aggregate Information with third parties. Rest assured, though, that Aggregate Information provided to third parties will not allow anyone to identify you, or determine anything personal about you. 

3.6 IP Addresses   
SKY may automatically receive and record information in our server logs from your browser, including your IP address (the Internet address of your PC), your computer's name, the type and version of your web browser, referrer addresses and other generally-accepted log information. We may also record page views (hit counts) and other general statistical and tracking information, which will be aggregated with that of other users in order to understand how our Website is being used. None of this data contains personally identifiable information. 

3.7 Cookies   
A cookie is a small amount of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser from a website's computers and stored on your computer's hard drive. Cookies can be used to provide you with a tailored user experience and to make it easier for you to use a website upon a future visit. We may include cookies on our Website and use them to recognize you when you return to our Website. You may set your browser so that it does not accept cookies. Cookies must be enabled on your web browser, however, if you wish to access certain personalized features of our Services. 

3.8 Computer Configuration   
In order to determine whether your computer is supported by our system, we may collect certain anonymous information. This information includes, but may not be limited to, your operating system and browser, as well as the presence of any software that our Website may require to operate with your computer, or other third party software on your computer. This information is kept strictly confidential and is not shared with third parties, except as provided for in this Privacy Policy. 

3.9 Extent of Information Collected   
We do not collect any more personally identifiable information than reasonably necessary to operate the Site, and respond to your requests. 

4\. We Do Not Disclose Information to Unaffiliated Third Parties; Limited Exceptions We use and disclose personally identifiable information as detailed in section 3, above. We will not otherwise disclose your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties without your express consent, except in the following limited circumstances: 

4.1 SKY Site Vendors   
We may employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf, such as (i) maintaining the Website, (ii) maintaining the server farm or farms that allow us to host your data, (iii) collecting information, (iv) responding to and sending electronic mail, or (vi) other functions necessary to our business. We may need to share your personally identifiable information with these companies (collectively, "Site Vendors"). We will provide Site Vendors with only that information necessary to perform their functions, and we will not allow them to use your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

4.2 Imminent Harm   
We may reveal your personally identifiable information to attorneys, private investigator organizations or law enforcement agencies if we believe (a) that you are in risk of harm from another, or (b) that you are harming or interfering (or will imminently harm or interfere) with others or violating (either intentionally or unintentionally) our Terms and Conditions of Use or otherwise violating legal rights. Please note, however, that by specifying this exception from our privacy and data protection practices, we assume no duty to monitor safety concerns on your behalf. 

4.3 Legal   
SKY will reveal your personally identifiable information, to the extent we reasonably believe we are required to do so by law, or in the unlikely event we become involved in a dispute with you, and such information is necessary to support or defend our position. In addition, if we receive legal process calling for the disclosure of your personally identifiable information we will attempt to notify you via the email address you supplied during registration within a reasonable amount of time before we respond to the request, unless such notification is not permitted. 

4.4 Transfer of Site   
SKY shall be entitled to transfer to a third party information it collects, including any personally identifiable information, in connection with a sale or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of the business entity responsible for the information under this Policy, provided the acquiring third party has agreed to safeguard your personally identifiable information with protections that in all material respects are the same as or more protective than those set out in this Privacy Policy. 

5\. Changing or Removing Information; Opting Out 

5.1 Discretionary Account Information   
To allow appropriate control over personally identifiable information, you can access the personally identifiable information you have provided to us via the Website, to change or update discretionary information that you have previously submitted. 

5.2 Opt-Out   
If we choose to send to you bulletins, updates, or other unsolicited communications that are marketing-related materials, we will provide you with the ability to decline - or "opt-out of" - receiving such communications. Instructions for opting-out will be provided if and when we determine to send you such a communication. Please understand that you will not be allowed to "opt-out" of formal notices concerning operation of this Website, and legal and other related notices concerning your relationship to the Site. 

5.3 Deleting Information   
Finally, if you request, we will remove your name and all other personally identifiable information from our databases compiled from the Site. Please understand, however, that it may be impossible to remove this information completely, due to backups and records of deletions. In addition, please understand that, if you request deletion of your information, you will be unable to utilize associated features of the Website and any associated services or information. You may not remove de-identified or Aggregate Information from our databases. 

6\. Security   
We have put in place security systems designed to prevent unauthorized access to or disclosure of information you provide to us, and we take reasonable steps to secure and safeguard this information, commensurate with the size and the demographics of SKY. 

Please understand, though, that we do not warrant as fail-proof the security of information provided by or submitted to SKY. Due to the nature of Internet communications and evolving technologies, we cannot provide, and disclaim, assurance that the information you provide us will remain free from loss, misuse, or alteration by third parties who, despite our efforts, obtain unauthorized access. 

7\. Privacy Protection for Children and Teens   
Our Website is not directed at children, and we will not accept or request personally identifiable information from individuals we know to be under 13. In accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"), if we learn that a child under 13 has provided personally identifiable information, we will either (i) delete this information from our databases, in accordance with our deletion policy, set out in Section 5.3, or (ii) obtain verifiable parental consent, in accordance with COPPA. 

8\. Notification of Changes   
From time to time, SKY may change its Privacy Policy. If we make any changes regarding disclosure of personally identifiable information to third parties, we will attempt to contact you prior to the date the modified policy is scheduled to take effect. We will post notice of the new Policy from the privacy link on our Website. With respect to Site Visitors, your use of our Site following any such change constitutes your agreement to follow and be bound by the Privacy Policy, as changed. With respect to Site Customers, no such changes will take effect unless and until you have provided us with your consent to such changes, in accordance with Sections 1.2 above. 

9\. Relationship to Terms of Use and Other Contracts   
This Privacy Policy must be read in conjunction with our Terms and Conditions of Use, and the provisions of our Terms and Conditions of Use are incorporated herein. To the extent the Terms and Conditions of Use conflict with the terms of this Privacy Policy, the terms of this Privacy Policy will control. 

10\. Contact Us You may contact us for any reason at the following addresses: 

Attention: Operations at SKYROAM   
Address: 820A Kifer Rd., Sunnyvale, CA 94086   
Email: support@skyroam.com 

11\. Effective Data The effective date of these Terms is July 1, 2011. 

COPYRIGHT AND LEGAL NOTICE.   
Copyright ©2011 Sky Travel Services Co., Limited. All Rights Reserved.
